A Monsterrific Musical!
Monster High: Boo York, Boo York is a animation,
family, music film directed by William Lau.
It's fright lights, big city when the Monster High ghouls head to Boo York!
Cleo de Nile is invited to attend a gancy gala celebrating the return of the
magical comet and, of course, she brings along her beast friends.
But their trip isn't all fun and frightseeing because Nefera, Cleo's sister,
uses the comet's power for her own spooktacularly sneaky plans.
Can the monsters unwrap the mystery of the comet in time to stop Nefera?
Find out in Booy York, Boo York, the first-ever Monster
High musical, featuring eight original songs.
Cleo de Nile / Clawdeen Wolf (voice), played by Salli Saffioti.
Catty Noir (voice), played by Missi Hale.
Pharaoh / Seth Ptolemy (voice), played by TJ Smith.
Deuce Gorgon / Agent (voice), played by Evan Smith.
Nefera de Nile (voice), played by Wendee Lee.
Frankie Stein (voice), played by Kate Higgins.
Monster High: Boo York, Boo York is a 2015 CGI-animated musical adventure fantasy children's film released on
home video on September 29 and broadcast on Nickelodeon as a television special on October 25.
Directed by William Lau and written by Keith Wagner, who also provided its story and screenplay, the film is the 9th in the
list of CGI-animated films and the 12 animated film overall based on the Monster High doll franchise by Mattel.
The soundtrack charted on Billboard's US Kid Albums and US Soundtracks.
The tone is lighthearted.